Jinro! Yay!
So, instead of playing wargames, we're going to play a game of wargames.
We're playing two songs, one at a time.
Oh, wow!
Wow!
This game is a survival game in which you are divided into two camps, werewolves and citizens, and fight for survival.
Have you ever played werewolf before?
Yes, I have.
No?
Yukino?
I did once, didn't I?
No, I haven't.
Oh, my God.
I'm sure it's the only one I'll ever have.
Ayaka?
Ayaka, but she's good.
Look at that.
I was a werewolf.
When we did it in the 7th season, I won alone.
Well, not just won... she was really good.
I've been working out a lot.
I was working out with my friends here.
But you too, Mako.
She's good, too.
She's a great singer.
If I were a werewolf, they'd know.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm looking at myself right now
Three.
So you're a werewolf now?
We're citizens now.
How many werewolves?
One.
Werewolves.
It's all about the werewolves, isn't it?
No knights.
I'm serious.
The pressure is too much.
I don't know.
I wonder who Urarashi is.
I'm sure you'll all make your guesses.
Which one?
It's important to have a good facial expression.
When you see it...
Scary!
Yuki's...
I don't know. He looks a little weak.
He's all big.
Worst.
The torch seems strong
Surprisingly true
Looks like he's smiling
The torch was very weak.
Surprisingly true.
The gym looks weak.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Revenge.
Will you shut up for once?
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Make sure the screen is visible to all players.
All players should be able to see it.
May we proceed with the game?
May I proceed?
Oh, my God.
When it starts to get dangerous...
Mr. Mobsy, Artificial Intelligence.
Mobsy.
I can't believe it's a name. It's so mob-ish.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Late-night installation.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Get ready.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I don't like this.
I'm scared. It's starting to feel like it's starting.
I kinda hate not having a knight.
What role does a knight play?
A protector.
That's true.
I don't like it.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God, it's behind the snow.
What?
Laughing.
So, seriously?
Yeah. - Wow.
Wow.
What? That's kind of funny.
Oh, man. That's nice.
Maybe this is the first time we're all going to the gym together after a show.
Exploring each other.
It's like a school trip.
Under the adults.
Who's that?
Who's there? Scary.
Oh, no.Oh no!
Your actions should match the barrage of the next player!
I'm strong.
Yes, you are.
I'm strong!
I'm really strong.
I'm so strong!
You're so proud of yourself!
I'm really strong.
When I played a lot of games with the newcomers in the 7th season.
I played werewolf.
I thought I was the last werewolf.
I don't remember.
I got a lot of "ehhhhh" from everyone.
I was YNN.
7th term
The first term was not so good, and there were not so many people doing it.
It's amazing!
Mr. Saka, you're in trouble.
I'm not here right now.
Misaki Sakata from YNN is going to be so in your face
Looks like it's coming out
She's super easy to recognize.
Mihina is easy to recognize
Risa seems easy to recognize
Light is strong
Seems strong.
It was strong!
Ami was easy to understand
Easy to understand.
Smile.
You're so funny!
They're all done.
Yes, sir.
What's with the air?
Scary.
Oh, no, I'm scared.
Oh, dazzling. You don't think dazzling will die?
First dazzling dies.
Oh, dazzling, dazzling, dazzling...
But not too thin.
It's kind of cute.
There's something not suspicious about it
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Multiple players, each with a different
what's up with that?
eh?
I couldn't get a read on it.
Oh, so it's already
So now they're all the same.
What?
Equal suspicion?
Oh, that too?
When you say "one"...
What?
We're all working on one person.
We've been talking for three minutes.
Oh, shit.
What are we all talking about? What are you all?
Citizens.
Citizens today.
Why do you only say "citizens"?
What?
Wait a minute.
Not yet?
Not yet.
Then let's hear about Sakura.
Yes, sir.
Citizens?
Wow.
That's weird.
Weird.
Well, then.
I'll tell you who I put in.
Oh, right.
Who was it?
Let's talk citizens.
Okay, okay.
One, two, three.
What?
The same?
I meant everyone's ni ni ni.
Uh...
Cape, Sakura, and Yukino?
Wow.
What?
I'm a werewolf with a thing for werewolves.
You've been acting a little smug.
Like it's me again.
No, this time it's not.
No, it's not.
It was sad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
So you're not a werewolf.
There's no knight.
You can't call him a fortune teller.
There's no one to protect him.
So the fortuneteller has no choice but to guide him.
That's true.Certainly.
Don't say you're a fortune teller.
Lead the werewolves away.
Fortune teller.
What about you, Yukino?
Everyone says so.
I'll give you an idea.
What's that?
Are you human?
Citizen?
I'm a human being.
Citizen.
Oh, I see.
Yukino was shocked when the two seniors stabbed her.
That's for sure.
That's right.
Sorry.
It's not like we're classmates... but seniors.
That's for sure.
I'm a citizen.
Today is the best day of my life.
I was
I was suspicious today.
What's wrong with you?
You're always smiling.
You're talking like a complete idiot.
I talk a lot.
I talk a lot when I'm not a werewolf.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How much of a citizen are you?
All creeps.
I'm a real citizen.
Oh, really?
Oh, I don't know, seriously.
He said it once.
Like Misaki Oana.
No, no.
This time it's for real.
I'm serious.
Serious.
Sad.
I mean, it's not as if...
Even the people who weren't stabbed are suspicious.
That's for sure.
What do you think?
Gio?
He's a citizen.
That's why you can't do anything.
Oh, yeah.
It's only 8 kilometers out.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's very suspicious.
I'm...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, Mr. Gio, Mr. Gio.
I'm a citizen.
Really?
Oh, my God.
I'm getting suspicious of people.
Really?
I'm serious.
This is for real.
It's just like me.
I can't say that.
You're serious.
I'm sorry.
You don't talk.
I can't stop looking at you like this.
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna get a tingle.
Wow!
Who's who?
Who do you think it is?
Let it be who you think it is
Yeah, right.
I don't know this time.
It's the first day. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't feel good.
Voting.
Voting time has arrived.
It is time to vote.
No, you're safe now.
I feel sorry for you.
Stay with Elevar.
Let's vote no.
Is it decided yet? No, not yet.
I haven't decided yet.
Wait, this hurts my heart.
It hurts my heart.
It's so bad.
Yay!Yay!
Yeah!
I don't know who to put in.
I don't know.
I guess that's what I call suspicious.
Not bad.
You can tell if a werewolf is smart by the people he kills.
I'm scared... scared...
That's scary.
You're going to kill your closest friends first?
Don't do that.
You're going to kill the talkers first?
I know exactly what you mean.
I'm not afraid of someone hitting me or someone stabbing me in the back.
I'm scared.
No one's died yet.
Who said we should play wargames?
Who is it?
Should I let the werewolves themselves?
I really love werewolves.
And I love Zion.
I used to play so much in elementary school.
I was young.
How long ago did you stop?
Really, like 10 years ago.
It's too funny.
I'm scared.
Let's move on to the next game, shall we?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared...
Objene
Ayapyon1 vote
Zion1 vote
Oh no decision vote
that's not true
Misaki1 vote
So this time
Misaki voted
I can't give you an answer yet.
Someone killed Misaki?
But he wasn't a werewolf.
Misaki, you're not a werewolf.
I told you.
I'm scared.
I'm going to go back out one more time.
There's been a communication error.
Wait a minute.
Sad.
App has woken up.
I'll restart it.
That's right, Misaki.
So you were a shiru.
You're a shiru.
Who let you in?
Who let Misaki in?
Come forward!
Who?
It's a discussion.
That's what I'm talking about.
On the other hand, who didn't?
Yukino.
He thought I had two votes.
I'm kind of glad.
That's great.
I'm a little happy.
It's a huge error.
Who's that?
You voted for Misaki, that's for sure.
You'll regret it later.
Because Misaki-san is a little upset.
I have to avenge Misaki-san's death.
That's for sure.
Who's that?
I'm scared.
They're all really suspicious.
But they're all dead.
Through the werewolves.
It's not B2's fault.
Don't do this, I swear.
This makes me want to do it all over again.
I want to.
Seventeen.
It would be so much fun if we all did it together.
I definitely want to do it.
I'm sure we'll have a lot of commitments.
With knights
Lay-bysh.
We're doing elevators and stuff.
If I get killed...
You're really strong, aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Please show your terminal to the player with the biggest catch.
Stop being so scary. I'm having a hard time voting.
I'm not going to lose. We're done.
We're all done.
That feels good, but...
Oh, my God, that's scary.
I'm scared! I'm scared someone's going to get killed!
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
I can't do it. I can't do it.I can't do this anymore. Makochi, Makochi, Makochi.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't think they'd kill Makocchi.
What? All of them?
That's pretty much it.
It's not what you think.
Yes.
The pine fence.
The pine fence is the most suspicious.
Discussion.
Is that so?
Oh, no.
What do you think?
I'm talking to him.
I'm laughing my ass off, but he's being a dick about it.
Oh, um...
What about the fortune teller?
What about the fortuneteller?
It could be true.
It could be either.
What, you're not a fortuneteller?
Den
Fortune teller.
Fortune teller?
Can we get a fortune teller now?
Not a fortune teller?
Shimin.
Shimin?
Fortune teller.
Was it?
No, you look like one.
You look like a fortune teller.
You're right, it does look like a fortune teller.
He was talking so much.
I can't talk, so now I feel really bad.
I feel sorry for him.
Wow.
He looks like a fortune teller.
You're serious.
Wow, so there's no fortune teller
I don't have a fortune teller.
Wow, really?
No more Mako.
What? Then werewolves are awesome!
I thought he was a fortuneteller.
You're right.
No, I saw what she said.
It's suspicious.
No, it's not.
I knew if I was on his side, he'd be too smart.
I thought I'd be exposed.
You're smart. You're smart.
You're smart.
No, I'm not.
I've seen the way your head looks.
It's a seep.
You know, if we were werewolves...
I'd change my character.
It's even more suspicious.
Wow!
I really am a smoker.
Even when I was a werewolf in my early days.
Shimin, shimin...
I just grinned.
Like this, it's like, "Oh, my God, I'm a werewolf!
I see.
You're smiling.
If you don't guess here...
If you don't guess here, you'll lose.
You're right.
Wow, wow, wow!
Now we're discussing who's going to be the fortune-teller.
What is it, guys? What is it, guys?
Uh, it's Shimin.
Ayaka...
Ayaka, you can't do anything now.
They must be really suspicious of you.
Yeah.
I seriously don't know if I'm a werewolf.
What?
I know.
Yeah, you did.
Oh, man. Well, let's just...
We'll talk about how it's going.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What, what, what, what?
You're not a Zeon?
What?
Yeah, but it's just a little bit...
It's a little bit like you're trying to make me look like a silly girl.
Like you did it.
Zion?
Yes, sir.
Oh, I'm sorry.
He was talking too much earlier.
He was like, "I killed that guy.
No, you didn't.
Oh, no.
Yeah, but Zion...
No, seriously not.
Yeah, but Zeon...Yeah, but Zion.
Who is it? Can I tell you who I voted for?
The guy who was just in here?
The one that got the shit kicked out of him earlier?
When you voted for Makocchi?
Who did I vote for?
Do you remember?
Maybe Miro was first.
No, sir.
Who did you put it in?
I put it in Mako.
Which one?
I'm sorry.
It's one or the other, isn't it?
No, it wasn't.
When Makocchi was killed earlier.
Yukino.
He's a citizen.
What?
Oh, no.
Isn't it bad?
Yes! Yes!
It's true.
Yukino.
We both see suspicious people differently.
Oh, no.
It's Yukino.
Yay!
Almost there.
I'll get your enemy.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Let's go for it.
But that's not what I meant.
Here
From here
You are also a player of Kosugi
Please turn your face
Please turn the player's face
I put it in the person who put it in first.
Shun shun in the snowy forest?
It's funny!
Oh, my God.
Snowy entrance?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Who is it?
Aya-pan
Oh no!
Oh, no...
Is it me? Thank you for everything.
I'm sad. You didn't believe me.
What? I get it now.
I really don't want to.
I don't know what to do.
And then...
It's over.
Hey, it's a win.
What if we don't?
What? Sad.
I don't know how to protect him.
Shirokoi.
Why not?
Fight Shirakoi.
This means we're losing
Here you go.
You mean it's true?
He's going to kill us.
Oh, no, no, no.
Your move of the night is fine.
It's too heavy.
Which one of us dies?
I can't.
Shurako.
It's all a bunch of nonsense.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore, it's so hard!
I didn't say that.
Let me see...
You're really scary
Oh, seriously...
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
That means I was right!
Who's the guy who did the "white love" thing?
He's a citizen.
You knew?
I was a fortune teller.
And if I saw these two first, I thought they'd be the citizens.
I thought it would be these two.
But they were the first to go?
Who was it?
I suspected these three first.
But then they went this way.
Then I narrowed it down to this one.
What? Why?
Citizens.Citizen.
But Mr. Zion does it without a plan.
It's lame.
Dull?
What?
Oh, no.
I knew it. I pulled over when we were alone.
Ten seconds.
Oh, no! I'm screwed!
I don't trust you anymore.
No, I can't.
Seriously?
I want to do it again.
If I confessed the night before that I was the fortuneteller...
This isn't the place.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
It's frustrating.
I don't like the way you're tying me up. What?
I trusted you to tell me.
I believed you, but when you distrust people...
I'll be fine...
voodoo b, 3rd floor
Thank you very much!
So I guess I'm like Mary!
Bye bye!